<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Code Coffee Compendium</title><link>http://learnteachcode.org/code-coffee-compendium/</link><description>Recent content on Code Coffee Compendium</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://learnteachcode.org/code-coffee-compendium/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Discussions and Articles</title><link>http://learnteachcode.org/code-coffee-compendium/discussions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://learnteachcode.org/code-coffee-compendium/discussions/</guid><description>Table of Contents Discussions and Articles Picking Up a Language or Framework Choosing a Text Editor or IDE Plain Text Editors Notepad++ Emacs or Vim Visual Studio Code IDEs IntelliJ PyCharm Eclipse Software Engineering Python Homepage | Tutorials and Challenges | How-To Guides | Discussions and Articles | References
Discussions and Articles Picking Up a Language or Framework Whether you&amp;#8217;re a brand new coder or a veteran, picking up a new tool can seem overwhelming.</description></item><item><title>How-To Guides</title><link>http://learnteachcode.org/code-coffee-compendium/how-to/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://learnteachcode.org/code-coffee-compendium/how-to/</guid><description>Table of Contents Community How-To Guides Python Open Source Homepage | Tutorials and Challenges | How-To Guides | Discussions and Articles | References
Community How-To Guides Python Automate the Boring Stuff with Python
Open Source How to Contribute to Open Source</description></item><item><title>References</title><link>http://learnteachcode.org/code-coffee-compendium/references/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://learnteachcode.org/code-coffee-compendium/references/</guid><description>Table of Contents References Programming Languages Frameworks Command Line Computer Science and Math Algorithms and Complexity Data Structures Computer Architecture Discrete Math Linear Algebra Statistics Logic Careers in Tech Software Engineering Data Science Electrical Engineering Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning Game Development Information Security Version Control Python Pair Programming System Design Homepage | Tutorials and Challenges | How-To Guides | Discussions and Articles | References</description></item><item><title>Tutorials and Challenges</title><link>http://learnteachcode.org/code-coffee-compendium/tutorials/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://learnteachcode.org/code-coffee-compendium/tutorials/</guid><description>Table of Contents Tutorials and Challenges Interactive Lessons &amp;amp; Challenges Learn a Tech Stack Interactive Coding Challenges Capture the Flag (CTF) Interactive Sandbox Environments Web Development Tutorials Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning Tutorials Information Security Tutorials Homepage | Tutorials and Challenges | How-To Guides | Discussions and Articles | References
Tutorials and Challenges Interactive Lessons &amp;amp; Challenges Learn a Tech Stack Learn a tech stack by doing interactive tutorials.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://learnteachcode.org/code-coffee-compendium/home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://learnteachcode.org/code-coffee-compendium/home/</guid><description>Introduction Welcome to the LearnTeachCode Code &amp;amp; Coffee Compendium! Maintained by the Baldwin Park &amp;amp; El Sereno/Alhambra study group, this page serves as a resource compendium for facilitating frequently asked questions of the form "Where should I go to learn &amp;lt;insert computer science topic&amp;gt;" at our meetup events. If you have any requests for particular resources, or would like to add one, please feel free to submit a https://github.</description></item></channel></rss>